{
    "subject": "Paul_Auster",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Lulu_on_the_Bridge",
    "human_readable": "Paul Auster directed the film Lulu on the Bridge.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9583098292350769,
            "question": "Who directed the film Lulu on the Bridge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8453079462051392,
            "question": "Who starred in Lulu on the Bridge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7952980399131775,
            "question": "Was Lulu on the Bridge a critically acclaimed film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7430492043495178,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Paul Auster?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7362837791442871,
            "question": "Where was Lulu on the Bridge filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7072502970695496,
            "question": "What is the plot of Lulu on the Bridge about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6210337281227112,
            "question": "What genre is the film Lulu on the Bridge likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5915502309799194,
            "question": "Is Paul Auster a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49940603971481323,
            "question": "Can you name other films directed by Paul Auster?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4716460406780243,
            "question": "Besides directing, what other works are associated with Paul Auster?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paul Auster directed the film Lulu on the Bridge.",
            "html": "yago_27473_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name other films directed by Paul Auster?",
            "html": "yago_27473_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Paul Auster a filmmaker?",
            "html": "yago_27473_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Lulu on the Bridge likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_27473_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27473_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27473_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27473_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27473_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27473_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27473_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27473_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27473_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27473_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27473_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because all the documents mention that Lulu on the Bridge was directed by Paul Auster."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide several pieces of information that support this statement. For instance, multiple files mention Paul Auster as the director of the film \"Lulu on the Bridge.\" Examples include:\n\n- The file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_27473/re-ranker-msmarco/10.txt states: \"LULU ON THE BRIDGE marks his solo debut as a director.\"\n- The file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_27473/re-ranker-msmarco/55.txt mentions Paul Auster directing the film.\n- The file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_27473/re-ranker-msmarco/108.txt also confirms that \"Lulu on the Bridge is a 1998 American romantic drama film directed by Paul Auster.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}